A Guide to the Social Science Research Council records, North Korea Program FA1776
Rockefeller Archive Center
Social Science Research Council records, North Korea Program
1968-2020
Rockefeller Archive Center
Social Science Research Council
Sigal, Leon (1942)
FA1776
52.5 Cubic Feet 138 document boxes: 137 letter boxes and 1 legal box
Scope and Contents
The collection contains the records of the Social Science Research Council's (SSRC) North Korea Program which was made up by the Northeast Asia Cooperative Security Project directed by Leon Sigal. The collection is comprised of one series that holds the files Sigal created through collecting news, articles, reports, and related materials about North Korea's nuclear program and the international politics associated with it. This information was gathered in service of the Project's mission of working in an unofficial capacity to end North Korea's nuclear and missiles programs. Sigal's collected materials primarily originate from between the early 1990s and 2020, but there are some earlier documents that date back to the late 1960s.
Common material formats found throughout the collection include news articles, newspaper clippings, reports, publications, interview and press briefing transcripts, testimony transcripts, correspondence, and unclassified government documents. Due to the bulk of materials being news articles, opinion pieces, and press statements by national governments, bias and offensive language may be found throughout the collection.
The collection also includes some records documenting the grant proposal and approval process for the Project.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
This material was transferred to the RAC from the Social Science Research Council in 2022 and was ingested by the RAC as Accession 2022:035.
Arrangement
Collection consists of one series.
Collection arrangement is as follows:
Series 1. Northeast Asia Cooperative Security Project, 1968-2020
Korea; Korea (North); Korea (South); United States; Japan; China; Russia; Human rights; National security; Nuclear nonproliferation; Nuclear weapons; Reconciliation; Security, International; Clippings (Books, newspapers, etc.)
- Northeast Asia Cooperative Security Project, 1968-2020; 1; 52.5 Cubic Feet 138 document boxes: 137 letter boxes and 1 legal box
  Scope and Contents
  The bulk of the series consists of materials Leon Sigal collected on North Korea's nuclear program and the associated international political contexts as part of his leadership of the Northeast Asia Cooperative Security Project for the Social Science Research Council. Materials Sigal collected include news articles, newspaper clippings, reports, publications, interview and press briefing transcripts, testimony transcripts, correspondence, and unclassified government documents. Correspondence in the series mostly comprises short messages people sent Sigal with articles and other items attached. Sigal authored several opinion articles collected within the series. News articles and clippings in the series largely come from media based in the United States, South Korea, and Japan. Many also appear to come from the Korean Central News Agency (KCNA) which is the North Korean state news agency.
  Most materials in the series originate from between the early 1990s and 2020, but there are some materials Sigal collected that were created as early as the late 1960s. Earlier documents are found mostly near the beginning of the series and are mostly declassified and archival documents.
  Subjects related to the North Korea nuclear and missiles program documented within the series include: - The network of international relations between North Korea (Democratic People's Republic of Korea; DPRK), South Korea (Republic of Korea; ROK), the United States, Japan, China, and Russia and how those relationships complicated the goal of ending North Korea's nuclear program but were also seen as an avenue for achieving nonproliferation or denuclearization, particularly through the 6 Party Talks - The political history of North Korea as well as South Korea, the U.S., and Japan in relation to those countries' North Korea foreign policy The capability of North Korea's nuclear and missiles programs with reference to topics like plutonium production, Light Water Reactor (LWR) technology, and missiles tests - International diplomacy efforts towards nonproliferation and/or denuclearization of the North Korea nuclear program including trilateral and multilateral approaches to diplomacy, track II diplomacy, involvement of the United Nations, the International Atomic Energy Agency (IAEA), inspections of possible nuclear materials and production facilities in North Korea, the U.S.-Noth Korea Agreed Framework, the Korean Peninsula Energy Development Organization (KEDO), and economic sanctions against North Korea - Relations between the two Koreas with focus on peace agreements between the two countries, the possibility of reunification, South Korea's Sunshine Policy towards North Korea, inter-Korean family reunions, the Korean Demilitarized Zone (DMZ), the Kaesong industrial park, possibilities for an inter-Korean railway, South Korea military drills, including joint drills with the U.S. military, Terminal High Altitude Area Defense (THAAD), the Cheonan sinking, South Korea issuing propaganda, and espionage - Nuclear weapons programs in other countries, purported connections between these other nuclear weapons programs and North Korea, and diplomatic and other approaches to ending those programs with reference to countries like Iran, Myanmar, and Syria among others and particular focus on the Iran nuclear deal framework - The issue of North Korean food security with discussion of famine, food shortages, and food aid to Noth Korea from other countries The impact of the War on Terror on international relations, the inclusion and removal of North Korea on the U.S.' terrorism list, the controversy of the Axis of Evil statement in President George W. Bush's State of the Union Adress, and the Iraq War - The legacy of Japanese militarism and its impact on Japan's relations with North Korea, South Korea, and China and the possibility of increased regional cooperation with particular focus on Japan recognizing and providing monetary compensation for comfort women, Japanese leaders visiting the Yasukuni Shrine, apologies by Japan for past actions, efforts to revise the pacifist Japanese constitution, and Japanese nationalism - Other and related topics documented in the series include: the condition of human rights in North Korea; the North Korean economy; people defecting from North Korea and North Korean refugees; cyber attacks; North Korean abductions of Japanese citizens and other foreign nationals; military relations between South Korea and the U.S., including the presence of U.S. troops in South Korea; energy aid to North Korea; North Korea money laundering; sea border disputes; North Korea satellite launches; and North Korean detainment of foreign nationals
  Individuals frequently discussed in relation to the subjects discussed above: - North Korea Supreme Leaders Kim Jong-il and Kim Jong-un - South Korea Presidents Kim Dae-jung, Roh Moo-hyun, Lee Myung-bak, Park Geun-hye, Moon Jae-in - United States Presidents George H.W. Bush, Bill Clinton, George W. Bush, Barack Obama, and Donald Trump - United States Secretaries of States Madeleine Albright, Colin Powell, Condoleezza Rice, Hillary Clinton, John Kerry, Rex Tillerson, Mike Pompeo - Other prominent U.S. diplomats Victor Cha, John Bolton, Robert Gallucci, John McCain - Japan Prime Ministers Junichiro Koizumi, Shinzo Abe, Yasuo Fukuda - China President Xi Jinping
  In addition to the aforementioned materials, there is a small amount of documents near the end of the series pertaining to the grant proposal process for the Northeast Asia Cooperative Security Project.
  - North Korea history - Articles, 1968-1996 (Box 1, Folder 1-4)
  - North Korea history, 1977-2011 (Box 1, Folder 5-6)
  - North Korea history, 1991-2009 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - North Korea history, 1986-2009 (Box 2, Folder 8-9)
  - North Korea history, 1983-2010 (Box 2, Folder 10-11)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 1, 1975-1998 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 2, 1990-1994 (Box 3, Folder 13-14)
  - Korea relations and politics, 1979-2002 (Box 3, Folder 15-17)
  - Korea relations and politics, 1992-1998 (Box 4, Folder 18-20)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 1, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 21-23)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 2, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Korea relations and politics, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 25-27)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 1, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 2, 1994-1996 (Box 6, Folder 29-30)
  - Korea relations and politics, 1977-1996 (Box 6, Folder 31-32)
  - Korea relations and politics, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 33-34)
  - Korea relations and politics, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 35-37)
  - Korea relations and politics, 1995-2013 (Box 7, Folder 38-39)
  - Korea relations and politics, 1996-1997 (Box 8, Folder 40-41)
  - Korea relations and politics, 1996-1998 (Box 8, Folder 42-43)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 1, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 2, 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 45-47)
  - Korea - President Richard Nixon administration, 1969-2010 (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Korea international politics and nuclear program, 1978-2010 (Box 9, Folder 49-50)
  - USS Pueblo - Cold War International History Project documents, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - Donald Rumsfeld Archive documents, 2000-2010 (Box 10, Folder 52)
  - South Korea nuclear program, 1974-2017 (Box 10, Folder 53)
  - Korea relations and politics, 1972-2012 (Box 10, Folder 54-56)
  - Conversation between Lee Hu-rak and Kim Il Sung - Wilson Center Digital Archive, 1972-2015 (Box 10, Folder 57)
  - Korea relations and politics, 1997-2017 (Box 11, Folder 58-61)
  - Korea relations and politics, 1998-2014 (Box 12, Folder 62-64)
  - Korea relations and politics, 1998-2017 (Box 12, Folder 65-67)
  - Korea relations and politics, 1998-2017 (Box 13, Folder 68-71)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 1, 1999-2017 (Box 13, Folder 72-73)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 2, 1999-2017 (Box 14, Folder 74)
  - Korea relations and politics, 1999-2004 (Box 14, Folder 75-77)
  - Korea relations and politics, 1999-2017 (Box 14, Folder 78-80)
  - Korea relations and politics, 1999-2004 (Box 15, Folder 81-84)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2000-2017 (Box 15, Folder 85-87)
  - 2000 Inter-Korean Summit, 2000-2017 (Box 16, Folder 88-89)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 90-92)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2000-2006 (Box 17, Folder 93-96)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 1, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 97)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 2, 2000-2004 (Box 18, Folder 98-99)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2001-2005 (Box 18, Folder 100-103)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2001-2005 (Box 19, Folder 104-107)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2001-2002 (Box 20, Folder 108-109)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 1, 2001-2002 (Box 20, Folder 110-112)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 2, 2001-2004 (Box 21, Folder 113)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2001-2010 (Box 21, Folder 114-118)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2001-2002 (Box 22, Folder 119-122)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2001-2002 (Box 23, Folder 123-126)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2002-2009 (Box 24, Folder 127-131)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 132-134)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 1, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 135-136)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 2, 2002 (Box 26, Folder 137)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2002-2006 (Box 26, Folder 138-141)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2002-2003 (Box 27, Folder 142-145)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 1, 2017 (Box 27, Folder 146-147)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 2, 2017 (Box 28, Folder 148-150)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2017-2018 (Box 28, Folder 151-153)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2017 (Box 29, Folder 154-156)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2018 (Box 29, Folder 157-159)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2018 (Box 30, Folder 160-161)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2017-2018 (Box 30, Folder 162-164)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2018 (Box 31, Folder 165-167)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2018 (Box 31, Folder 168-170)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2018 (Box 32, Folder 171-173)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 1, 2018 (Box 32, Folder 174-176)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 2, 2018 (Box 33, Folder 177)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2003-2006 (Box 33, Folder 178-181)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2003-2005 (Box 34, Folder 182-185)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2003 (Box 35, Folder 186-189)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 1, 2003 (Box 35, Folder 190-191)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 2, 2003 (Box 36, Folder 192-193)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2003-2009 (Box 36, Folder 194-196)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 1, 2003-2005 (Box 36, Folder 197-198)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 2, 2003-2004 (Box 37, Folder 199)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2003 (Box 37, Folder 200-201)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2003-2004 (Box 37, Folder 202-204)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2004 (Box 38, Folder 205-207)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 1, 2004 (Box 38, Folder 208-210)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 2, 2004 (Box 39, Folder 211-212)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2004 (Box 39, Folder 213-215)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2003-2008 (Box 40, Folder 216-218)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 1, 2004-2013 (Box 40, Folder 219-220)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 2, 2004 (Box 41, Folder 221-222)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2004 (Box 41, Folder 223-225)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2003-2006 (Box 42, Folder 226-228)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 229-230)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2004 (Box 43, Folder 231-234)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 1, 2004 (Box 43, Folder 235)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 2, 2004-2005 (Box 44, Folder 236-237)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2004 (Box 44, Folder 238-239)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 1, 2004 (Box 44, Folder 240-241)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 2, 2004-2005 (Box 45, Folder 242-243)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2005 (Box 45, Folder 244-245)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 1, 2005 (Box 45, Folder 246-247)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 2, 2005-2007 (Box 46, Folder 248-249)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2005-2006 (Box 46, Folder 250-253)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2005 (Box 47, Folder 254-257)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 1, 2005 (Box 47, Folder 258-259)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 2, 2005 (Box 48, Folder 260-263)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 1, 2005 (Box 48, Folder 264-265)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 2, 2005 (Box 49, Folder 266-267)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2005-2007 (Box 49, Folder 268-270)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2005-2006 (Box 50, Folder 271-273)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 1, 2005 (Box 50, Folder 274-275)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 2, 2005-2007 (Box 51, Folder 276)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2005-2007 (Box 51, Folder 277-279)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 1, 1993-2005 (Box 51, Folder 280)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 2, 2005 (Box 52, Folder 281-282)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2005-2006 (Box 52, Folder 283-285)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 1, 2006-2007 (Box 52, Folder 286)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 2, 2006 (Box 53, Folder 287-288)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2005-2006 (Box 53, Folder 289-291)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2006 (Box 54, Folder 292-294)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2005-2006 (Box 54, Folder 295-297)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2006 (Box 55, Folder 298-300)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 1, 2003-2006 (Box 55, Folder 301-302)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 2, 2006 (Box 56, Folder 303)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 1, 2006-2011 (Box 56, Folder 304-307)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 2, 2006 (Box 57, Folder 308)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2006 (Box 57, Folder 309-311)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 1, 2004-2006 (Box 57, Folder 312-313)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 2, 2006 (Box 58, Folder 314)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 1, 2006-2009 (Box 58, Folder 315-318)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 2, 2006-2008 (Box 59, Folder 319-320)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 1, 2006 (Box 59, Folder 321-323)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 2, 2006 (Box 60, Folder 324)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2006-2008 (Box 60, Folder 325-327)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 1, 2007 (Box 60, Folder 328)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 2, 2007 (Box 61, Folder 329-331)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 1, 2002 (Box 61, Folder 332-333)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 2, 2002-2003 (Box 62, Folder 334-335)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 1, 2003-2006 (Box 62, Folder 336-337)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 2, 2003-2005 (Box 63, Folder 338-340)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 1, 2003-2006 (Box 63, Folder 341-342)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 2, 2003 (Box 64, Folder 343-344)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 1, 2002-2003 (Box 64, Folder 345-347)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 2, 2003-2005 (Box 65, Folder 348)
  - PBS Frontline: Kim's Nuclear Gamble interviews, 2003 (Box 65, Folder 349)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 1, 2002-2005 (Box 65, Folder 350-352)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 2, 2002-2003 (Box 66, Folder 353)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2006-2008 (Box 66, Folder 354-357)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2006-2007 (Box 67, Folder 358-361)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2006-2007 (Box 68, Folder 362-365)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 1, 2007 (Box 68, Folder 366)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 2, 2007 (Box 69, Folder 367)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2007 (Box 69, Folder 368-370)
  - Banco Delta Asia (BDA), 2005-2007 (Box 69, Folder 371)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2007 (Box 70, Folder 372-374)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2007 (Box 70, Folder 375-376)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2007-2018 (Box 71, Folder 377-379)
  - Korean relations and politics, part 1, 2007 (Box 71, Folder 380)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 2, 2007 (Box 72, Folder 381-383)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 1, 2007 (Box 72, Folder 384)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 2, 2007 (Box 73, Folder 385)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2007-2008 (Box 73, Folder 386-387)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 1, 2008 (Box 73, Folder 388)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 2, 2008 (Box 74, Folder 389-390)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2008 (Box 74, Folder 391-392)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2007-2008 (Box 74, Folder 393-394)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2008 (Box 75, Folder 395-397)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2008 (Box 75, Folder 398-399)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2008 (Box 76, Folder 400-401)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2008 (Box 76, Folder 402-403)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 1, 2008 (Box 76, Folder 404)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 2, 2007-2009 (Box 77, Folder 405)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2008-2009 (Box 77, Folder 406-408)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 1, 2009 (Box 77, Folder 409)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 2, 2008-2009 (Box 78, Folder 410)
  - Korea relations and politics, 1967-2009 (Box 78, Folder 411-413)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2008-2018 (Box 79, Folder 414-415)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2008 (Box 79, Folder 416-417)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 1, 2008 (Box 79, Folder 418)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 2, 2008 (Box 80, Folder 419)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2008 (Box 80, Folder 420-421)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 1, 2009 (Box 80, Folder 422-423)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 2, 2009-2010 (Box 81, Folder 424-425)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2009 (Box 81, Folder 426-428)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2009 (Box 82, Folder 429-431)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 1, 2009 (Box 82, Folder 432)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 2, 2009-2010 (Box 83, Folder 433-434)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2009-2011 (Box 83, Folder 435-437)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2009-2011 (Box 84, Folder 438-440)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2009-2011 (Box 84, Folder 441-442)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2010-2011 (Box 85, Folder 443-445)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2010-2014 (Box 85, Folder 446-448)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2010 (Box 86, Folder 449-451)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2010 (Box 86, Folder 452-454)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2010 (Box 87, Folder 455-458)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 1, 2009-2011 (Box 87, Folder 459)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 2, 2009-2011 (Box 88, Folder 460-461)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 1, 2009-2013 (Box 88, Folder 462-463)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 2, 2009-2011 (Box 89, Folder 464)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2013 (Box 89, Folder 465-467)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 1, 2012-2013 (Box 89, Folder 468)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 2, 2013 (Box 90, Folder 469)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2013 (Box 90, Folder 470-471)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2013 (Box 90, Folder 472-473)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2013 (Box 90, Folder 474-475)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2013 (Box 91, Folder 476-477)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2013 (Box 91, Folder 478-479)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 1, 2013 (Box 91, Folder 480)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 2, 2013 (Box 92, Folder 481)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2014 (Box 92, Folder 482-483)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2014 (Box 92, Folder 484-485)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2014 (Box 93, Folder 486-487)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2014 (Box 93, Folder 488-490)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2014 (Box 94, Folder 491-492)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2014 (Box 94, Folder 493)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2014 (Box 94, Folder 494-495)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2014 (Box 95, Folder 496-497)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2014 (Box 95, Folder 498-499)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2014 (Box 95, Folder 500-501)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2014 (Box 96, Folder 502)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2014 (Box 96, Folder 503-504)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 1, 2010-2011 (Box 96, Folder 505-506)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 2, 2007-2010 (Box 97, Folder 507-508)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2010-2011 (Box 97, Folder 509-511)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2010-2012 (Box 98, Folder 512-514)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 1, 2010 (Box 98, Folder 515)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 2, 2007-2010 (Box 99, Folder 516-518)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 1, 2010 (Box 99, Folder 519)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 2, 2009-2010 (Box 100, Folder 520)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2010-2011 (Box 100, Folder 521-523)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 1, 2010 (Box 100, Folder 524)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 2, 2010 (Box 101, Folder 525-526)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2011 (Box 101, Folder 527-528)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2011 (Box 102, Folder 529-530)